Now I'll go through the profile and
الآن سأستعرض الملف الشخصي
give you my thoughts, the profile picture seems a little juvenile.
وأعطيكم رأيي فيه. تبدو صورة الملف الشخصي صبيانية بعض الشيء،
And you can't see the face clearly,
ولا يمكن رؤية الوجه بوضوح.
it would be better to have a normal picture without a crazy filter.
لكان من الأفضل أن تكون لدينا صورة عادية دون مرشّح جنوني.
We also don't know what this user's real name is,
كما لا نعرف أيضاً الاسم الحقيقي لهذا المستخدم.
the username acorn47 could be better, something based off the real name.
يمكن اختيار اسم مستخدم أفضل من acorn47، مثل اسم يستند إلى الاسم الحقيقي.
There isn't any other personal information either,
كما ليست هناك أي معلومات شخصية أخرى هنا.
if I was a recruiter, I wouldn't know how to contact this person.
لو كنت مسؤول توظيف، لما عرفت كيفية الاتصال بهذا الشخص،
Or anything about this person really,
بل لما عرفت أي شيء عن هذا الشخص.
descriptions of their repository would be very useful here.
لكان وضع توصيفات لمستودعاته مفيداً للغاية هنا،
So I can tell what kind of projects this person has worked on, and
حتى أتمكن من معرفة أي نوع من المشاريع التي عمل عليها هذا الشخص،
finally we can look at the contribution chart.
وأخيراً يمكننا أن ننظر إلى مخطط المساهمات.
There's a bunch of commits here, then a couple commits later,
هناك مجموعة من التعديلات المحفوظة هنا ثم تعديلان محفوظان في وقت لاحق،
this person appears to not have spent much time writing code.
يبدو أن هذا الشخص لم يمض وقتاً طويلاً في كتابة التعليمات البرمجية.
It's possible they made a lot of changes, but
من المحتمل أنه قام بالكثير من التغييرات،
packed everything into one large commit, that's not a good sign.
ولكنه حصر كل شيء في تعديل واحد كبير، وهذه ليست علامة جيدة.